(Raj:)Oh, snap.
[CHUCKLES]
(Sheldon:)Snap what?
- Okay, I guess we have to turn to plan B.
- What's plan B?
Erase the hard drives, grab the tapes, wipe
our fingerprints off every surface and run.
(Sheldon:)Why wasn't that plan A?
ANNOUNCER [ON TV]: A NASA spokesman
states that due to the loss of data...
...they will most likely be unable
to determine the cause...
...of the Mars rover's malfunction.
(Howard:)Thank God for plan B.
(Penny:)Howard, didn't you say
you worked on the Mars rover?
(Howard:)No, you're mistaken.
(Penny:)Yeah, when we first met.
(Penny:)You said that if I went out with you
I could drive a car on Mars.
(Howard:)I don't know what you're talking about.
LEONARD:
Psst?
(Sheldon:)Will you all excuse me?
Leonard is signaling
that he'd like to talk to me in private.